Guide to the Industrial Union of Marine and Shipbuilding Workers of America Local 61 Records, 1943-1990 AIS.1989.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Allegheny Conference on Human Development, II.
  - The Pittsburgh Foundation: The Many Ways It Works for Donors (Box 78, Item 1)
  - The New Republic, June 22, 1987 (Box 78, Item 2)
  - Pitt at 201: A Founders Day Album (Box 78, Item 3)
  - Carnegie Magazine, January-February 1988 (Box 78, Item 4)
  - Pittsburgh: New Spring Books by University of Pittsburgh Press, 1988 (Box 78, Item 5)
  - PHLF News, 1987 (Box 78, Item 6-7)
  - The Pioneer Story, 1928-1986: A Guide to Professional Investing by The Pioneers Group, Inc. (Box 78, Item 8)
  - Jewish Appointment Calendar, 1987-1988 (Box 78, Item 9)
  - Network to Save the Mon/Ohio Valley T-Shirt (Box 78, Item 10)
  - Save Our Shipbuilders T-Shirt (Box 78, Item 11)